Young Master,
I have the results of the investigation
into the missing dock workers.
It's exactly as you thought.
I asked around
the Qingtian Gang's territory.
Recently, a group of people
did have inexplicable accidents.
Here is the list.
The beggar on East Street,
the orphan at the chapel,
and the old mute at the ferry.
They really know how to pick them.
These people are just like Zheng.
No one cares even if they die.
Our people also found something else.
In these places,
they all saw Wu Ren.
It seems something happened in Ningcheng,
and it's related to the Shisha Gang.
Maybe Shen Tianbai and Wu Ren
are plotting something,
or maybe...
Shen Tianbai is a spy sent
by Wu Ren to the Shisha Gang.
Of course, this is just a guess.
I need to find out what Shen Tianbai
is up to as soon as possible.
He is very cautious.
I'm afraid it won't be easy.
I'm going to put on a show tomorrow.
I'll take a gamble.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 13]
Hui.
Where is your lackey?
How is he?
Is the sack comfortable to sleep in?
Lu Ye.
You are all alone,
yet you dare to run wild
in our Shisha Gang's territory.
So what if I'm alone?
You're a loser anyway.
What did you say?
I said you're a loser.
Are you deaf?
You!
Lu Ye.
You've come at me so many times,
yet I'm still standing here
perfectly fine.
Even in your territory,
you don't dare to make a move.
Coward.
You brat,
you asked for it.
Tianbai, let's go.
Young Master! Young Master!
What's wrong?
Where are you hurt?
Young Master.
Let's go.
Careful, careful.
Careful.
Here, give it to me.
The young master's wound is infected.
Go get some antibiotics immediately.
The sooner, the better!
Yes.
Go quickly.
[Breaking: Lu Ye Unconscious
for 24 Hours;]
[Qingtian Gang Thrown into Chaos;
Hefty Reward for High‑effect Antibiotics]
Thank God.
That brat Lu Ye's wound must be infected.
My dagger was just dipped
in the dirty water from the dock.
He's doomed to die this time.
Hui.
Tell me about it.
Here.
You really want to know?
Let me tell you.
If ordinary antibiotics could cure it,
the Qingtian Gang
wouldn't go to such great lengths.
They must use a specific medicine.
However,
in the entire Ningcheng right now,
they will definitely not find it.
Hui,
why?
Why?
Because the medicine
is in the boss's study.
They would never expect it.
Lu Ye clearly provoked Hui that day.
Why was he so reckless?
But what if...
Forget it.
He needs this medicine without delay.
Forget it, I'll just take a look.
Oh no.
It's a trap.
Guard the door well!
-Yes!
Officer Shen.
Since you're here,
why are you in such a hurry to leave?
Shen Tianbai,
you've let me go so many times.
And...
you still want to save me.
You are an undercover agent sent
by the police to the Shisha Gang.
Quite an imagination you've got.
Aren't you?
Then why didn't you let me die?
Is there any other reason?
I don't want you to die.
If you die, the Qingtian Gang
will fall apart.
Without enemies, how can I climb?
My apologies.
So you have such great ambitions.
You want to be the boss
of the Shisha Gang?
Can't I?
There's not a grain of truth in anything
that old guy Wu Ren says.
He told me something happened
in Ningcheng,
so he had to send you to the Shisha Gang
as an undercover agent.
It seems I didn't hit him hard enough.
Where is my master?
You fell for it.
I'm really sorry,
Officer Shen.
I lied to you again.
You tricked me.
Can't I?
This was accidentally left by Wu Ren
when he went to the ferry to investigate.
I don't have the ability
to kidnap your master.
Accidentally?
Fine.
I admit
I asked the people
of the Qingtian Gang to take it.
What about your injury?
This is true.
Your injury is very serious,
and your life is in danger?
That's a little exaggerated.
What exactly do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
Since you are so smart,
don't you know?
I don't want to know.
My father's death
is related to the Shisha Gang.
It's also related to the drugs
you are investigating.
I don't want to be kept in the dark.
No matter what you are doing now,
count me in.
I will help you find
the real murderer of your father.
But you don't need
to participate in other things.
Help?
I want to be in the game.
No way.
Then don't blame me
for telling him your little secret.
Whether Xu Qingdao believes it or not
doesn't really matter.
What matters is...
Once people
become suspicious...
Is this how you bite the hand
that feeds you?
Thank you for giving me
this chance to threaten you.
Why should I trust
someone like you?
This is my show of good faith.
With this,
you can access
the core of the Qingtian Gang.
I promise
I will help you climb the ranks
until Xu Qingdao trusts you.
By then,
we will be able
to get the answers we want.
What do you say?
Do you want to cooperate with me?
I hope this time,
you won't make me regret it.
Definitely not.
What's wrong?
I didn't even use much force.
Shen Tianbai.
Are you poisoned?
Xu Qingdao.
He's controlling you with drugs.
Xu Qingdao did this.
Right?
What is the antidote for this poison?
Xu Qingdao gives me
the antidote every 2 weeks.
That's a huge price to pay.
Then we have even more reason to succeed.
No matter what the police want to do,
once the truth is revealed,
I will definitely kill Xu Qingdao.
If only it were that simple.
Xu Qingdao is just a pawn.
The medicine is all in the boss's study.
It serves another purpose.
They don't know.
What purpose?
Why do you care what it's for?
Anyway, the person
above the boss needs it.
When we send it to him,
we'll get the credit too.
Who is that person?
That person.
He is that person.
Behind him,
there is someone else.
What?